Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- R, 11193
  - Rosenthal, Seymour, undated; cuid2013; 11248 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Rosenzweig, Carl, undated; cuid2014; 11249 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Ross, Gerald, undated; cuid2015; 11251 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Ross, Ian, undated; cuid2016; 11252 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Ross, Keith, 2004; cuid2017; 11253 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Rossoff, undated; cuid2018; 11254 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Roth, George Col., 1933; cuid2019; 11255 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Rothbard, Murray, undated; cuid2020; 11256 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Rothschild, Fred, undated; cuid2021; 11257 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Rothschild, Walter N., Jr., undated; cuid2022; 11258 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Rowley, Louis N., Jr., 1976, 1968, 1978; cuid2023; 11259 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Roy, Dipak, undated; cuid2024; 11260 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Ruben, Samuel, 1979; cuid2025; 11261 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Rubenstein, Charlie, undated; cuid2026; 11262 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Rubin, cuid2027; 14791 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Rudin, Paul, undated; cuid2028; 11263 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Ruppel, Alfred E., circa 1975; cuid2029; 11264 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Russell, Edward, 1954, 1972; cuid2030; 11265 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Russell, Joan, 1983; cuid2031; 11266 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Russell, Jules, circa 1954; cuid2032; 11267 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Russell, William M., cuid2033; 14792 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Russo, Onofrio "Nick", circa 1998; cuid2034; 11268 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Ruten, William H., undated; cuid2035; 11269 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Ryan, Albert J., Lt. Col., 1954-1955; cuid2036; 11270 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Ryan, John F., 1931; cuid2037; 11271 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- S, 11326
  - Sabavala, Darius, undated; cuid2038; 11272 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Sabet, M., undated; cuid2039; 11273 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Sacher, Alex, undated; cuid2040; 11274 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Sack, Edgar A., undated; cuid2041; 11275 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Saidla, Leo E.A., 1952; cuid2042; 11276 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Sakai, Wataru, undated; cuid2043; 11277 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Salkind, Alvin J., undated; cuid2044; 11278 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Saltman, Bethany, undated; cuid2045; 11279 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Salzinger, Kurt, 1982, 1985; cuid2046; 11280 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Sanator, Robert J., 1980, 1984; cuid2047; 11281 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Sannizjari, Salvatore, undated; cuid2048; 11282 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Sarno, Frank J., undated; cuid2049; 11283 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Savitt, Sidney A., 1983, 1985; cuid2050; 11284 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Sawyer, 1951; cuid2051; 11285 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Sawyer, Fred, undated; cuid2052; 11286 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Sbasching, Richard W., 2001; cuid2053; 11287 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Sbordone, George J., undated; cuid2054; 14822 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Schaaf, undated; cuid2055; 11288 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Schachter, 1986; cuid2056; 11289 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Schaefer, John P., undated; cuid2057; 11290 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Schaffner, Charles E., 1955; cuid2058; 11291 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Schallcross, Lewis, undated; cuid2059; 11292 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Schatter, Arnie, undated; cuid2060; 11293 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Schein, Eugene, undated; cuid2061; 11294 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Scheiner, Lowell, undated; cuid2062; 11295 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Scher, Seymour, 1982; cuid2063; 11296 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Schilling, Ronald, undated; cuid2064; 11297 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Schillinger, A. George, undated; cuid2065; 11298 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Schlect, Matt, undated; cuid2066; 11299 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Schleher, Daniel Curtis, undated; cuid2067; 11300 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Schleich, Donald, 1986; cuid2068; 11301 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Schleuning, Herbert W., undated; cuid2069; 11302 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Schmidling, David, undated; cuid2070; 11303 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Schmidt, Harry, undated; cuid2071; 11304 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Schmidt, Jeanette, undated; cuid2072; 11305 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Schroeder, Robert W., undated; cuid2073; 11306 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Schuck, O. Hugo, undated; cuid2074; 11307 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Schuck, Robert E., 1970; cuid2075; 11308 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Schurig, W. Fred, undated; cuid2076; 11309 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Schuler, Raymond T., undated; cuid2077; 11310 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Schuster, Seymour, undated; cuid2078; 11311 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Schwalb, Allen J., 1995; cuid2079; 11312 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Schwalm, William H., undated; cuid2080; 11313 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Schwartz, Jerome, undated; cuid2081; 11314 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Scicutella, John, undated; cuid2082; 11315 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Scott, C.F., undated; cuid2083; 11316 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Scott, Shannon, undated; cuid2084; 11317 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Seidenberg, Ivan, undated; cuid2085; 11318 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Sekimoto, Tadahiro, 1998; cuid2086; 11319 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Selby, Harold E., 1960; cuid2087; 11320 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Selesnick, Ivan, undated; cuid2088; 11321 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Senitzky, Benjamin, undated; cuid2089; 11322 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Sepahbin, Amir H., undated; cuid2090; 11323 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Setterstrom, Carl A., undated; cuid2091; 11324 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Settle, Sandy, undated; cuid2092; 11325 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Severance, Dennis, cuid2093; 11327 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Sforza, Pasquale, 1993; cuid2094; 11328 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Shah, Chandni, undated; cuid2095; 11329 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Shamis, Sidney S., undated; cuid2096; 11330 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Shang, Joseph S., undated; cuid2097; 11331 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Shapiro, Lawrence, undated; cuid2098; 11332 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Shavers, Sgt., undated; cuid2099; 11333 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Shaw, Leonard, 1986, 1994; cuid2100; 11334 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Sheldon, Rufus, undated; cuid2101; 11335 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Sheldon, Samuel, undated; cuid2102; 11336 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Shepherd, Donald S., 1980; cuid2103; 11337 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Sheverev, Valery, undated; cuid2104; 11338 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Shields, B.A., undated; cuid2105; 11339 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Shinn, Richard R, undated; cuid2106; 11340 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Shmoys, Jerry, 1967; cuid2107; 11341 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Shnidman, Yitzahak, undated; cuid2108; 11342 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Shooman, Martin, 1974, 1998; cuid2109; 11343 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Shultis, Christine, circa 1996; cuid2110; 11344 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Shustek, Leonard, 1997-1998; cuid2111; 11345 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Sibner, Leslie, undated; cuid2112; 11346 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Siderer, Jack, undated; cuid2113; 11347 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Sie, John J., circa 1996; cuid2114; 11348 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Silber, Leo M., undated; cuid2115; 11349 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Sill, Joshua Woodrow (1831-1862), undated; cuid2116; 11350 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Silleck, Clarence F., 1963, 1983, 1985; cuid2117; 11351 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Silver, Sheldon, undated; cuid2118; 11352 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Simanca, Santiago, undated; cuid2119; 11353 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Simins, Herbert J., 1977; cuid2120; 11354 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Simmonds, G., undated; cuid2121; 11355 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Simo, Constance, undated; cuid2122; 11356 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Singer, Gerald, 1968; cuid2123; 11357 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Singer, Henry, 1994; cuid2124; 11358 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Singer, Joel, undated; cuid2125; 11359 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sipress, Jack, circa 1995; cuid2126; 11360 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sirota, Julius, undated; cuid2127; 11361 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Sitock, George, 1950s; cuid2128; 11362 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sivetz, Michael, undated; cuid2129; 11363 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sjuren, Harold, 2000; cuid2130; 11364 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Skrzypczak, Casmir, undated; cuid2131; 11365 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Skurla, George M., circa 1982; cuid2132; 11366 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Slack, 1954; cuid2133; 11367 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Slaughter, John B., undated; cuid2134; 11368 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Slutsky, Simon, 1978; cuid2135; 11369 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Slyke, Richard Van, undated; cuid2136; 11370 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Smith, E. B. L., undated; cuid2137; 11371 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Edward J., 1964; cuid2138; 11372 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Gregory D., undated; cuid2139; 11373 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Harrison, undated; cuid2140; 11374 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Smith, James M., 2000; cuid2141; 11375 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Smith, Joseph S., undated; cuid2142; 11376 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Kate, undated; cuid2143; 11377 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Stanley, undated; cuid2144; 11378 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Snitroff, Joseph, undated; cuid2145; 11383 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Snyder, Joel, 1996; cuid2146; 11384 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Soehngen, Henry F., undated; cuid2147; 11385 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Soffer, Jonathan, undated; cuid2148; 11386 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Sokolsky, Saul, undated; cuid2149; 11387 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Solimene, Nicholas, undated; cuid2150; 11388 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Sonnenfeldt, Richard, undated; cuid2151; 11389 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Soros, Paul, undated; cuid2152; 11390 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Soutar, Charles F., circa 1997; cuid2153; 11391 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Soviero, Joseph C., circa 1996; cuid2154; 11392 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Sparacino, Robert R., undated; cuid2155; 11393 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Spellane, Peter, undated; cuid2156; 11394 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Spenadel, Paul, undated; cuid2157; 11395 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Spencer, William J., 1987; cuid2158; 11396 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Sprinsky, William Lt. Col., undated; cuid2159; 11397 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Spruclt, Albert E., undated; cuid2160; 11398 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Squire, Edward J., 1956; cuid2161; 11399 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Stancu, Alina, undated; cuid2162; 11400 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - St. Lawrence, Jim, undated; cuid2163; 11401 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Steck, Paul G., undated; cuid2164; 11402 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Steele, Stuart, undated; cuid2165; 11403 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Stefanis, Anthony, undated; cuid2166; 11404 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Steigman, Joseph, undated; cuid2167; 11405 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Steil, Leonard, undated; cuid2168; 11406 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Stein, Richard S., undated; cuid2169; 11407 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Stein, Sidney J., undated; cuid2170; 11408 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Steinberg, Gerald M., 1956; cuid2171; 11409 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Steingut, Stanley, undated; cuid2172; 11410 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Steneck, Eugene, undated; cuid2173; 11411 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Sterling Drug, undated; cuid2174; 11412 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Sterling, Frank, undated; cuid2175; 11413 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Sterling, John, undated; cuid2176; 11414 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Stern, Henry Root, undated; cuid2177; 11415 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Sternberg, Sy, circa 2006; cuid2178; 11416 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Stevens, Joseph, undated; cuid2179; 11417 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Stever, H. Guyford, 1975; cuid2180; 11418 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Stidham, James A., 1956; cuid2181; 11419 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Stiel, Leonard, undated; cuid2182; 11420 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Stoll, Eric D., undated; cuid2183; 11421 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Stolze, William, 1959, 1981; cuid2184; 11422 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Stouraitis, Thanos, undated; cuid2185; 11423 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Strang, Charles D., 1985; cuid2186; 11424 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Strauss, Fred J., undated; cuid2187; 11425 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Strauss, Simon D., 1977, 1986; cuid2188; 11426 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Streubel, Ernest John, circa 1948; cuid2189; 11427 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Strom, Gordon, undated; cuid2190; 11428 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Strybing, Herman Frederick, 1880s (reproductions); cuid2191; 11429 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Suarez, Humbert, undated; cuid2192; 11430 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Sudarsky, Jerry M., 1964, 1971, 1974; cuid2193; 11431 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Suel, Torsten, undated; cuid2194; 11432 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Sull, Won Bong, undated; cuid2195; 11433 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Sulzer, Henri G., undated; cuid2196; 11434 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Sun, Yun-Suan, undated; cuid2197; 11435 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Sung, Peter, circa 1987; cuid2198; 11436 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Suttles, Sandy, undated; cuid2199; 11437 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Sviedrys, Romualdes, 1975; cuid2200; 11438 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Swackhamer, Farris S., undated; cuid2201; 11439 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Swan, David, undated; cuid2202; 11440 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Swanson, Jeanne, undated; cuid2203; 11441 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Swartz, Jerome, undated; cuid2204; 11442 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Sweeney, Richard, 1986; cuid2205; 11443 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Sylvester, William R., circa 1980; cuid2206; 11444 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Szeglin, Arthur, undated; cuid2207; 11445 (Box 8, Folder 89)
- T, 11446
  - Tai, Meihua, undated; cuid2208; 11447 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Talberth, Henry, undated; cuid2209; 11448 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Talley, Charles P., 1982; cuid2210; 11449 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Tam, Wai Nam, undated; cuid2211; 11450 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Tamir, Theodor, undated; cuid2212; 11451 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Teng, Hualiang (Harry), undated; cuid2213; 11452 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Teraoka, Iwao, undated; cuid2214; 11453 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Terzouli, Andrew J., undated; cuid2215; 11454 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Tesoro, Giuliana, circa 1986; cuid2216; 11455 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Tevonian, Ronald, circa 1998; cuid2217; 11456 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Thevanayagam, Theva, undated; cuid2218; 11457 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Thomas, Daniel J., 1950s; cuid2219; 11458 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Thompson, Carol, undated; cuid2220; 11459 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Thompson, Harley, undated; cuid2221; 11460 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Thompson, Michael, 2009; cuid2222; 11461 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Thorne, undated; cuid2223; 11462 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Thorsen, Richard, 1980, 1986, 1998; cuid2224; 11463 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Throndsen, Elton C., 1955; cuid2225; 11464 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Thurber, Elmer, undated; cuid2226; 11465 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Tobias, Abraham Joel, 1960s; cuid2227; 11466 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Todd, Leonard, undated; cuid2228; 11467 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Tongobarch, Vincent, undated; cuid2229; 11468 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Tooney, Nancy, 1986; cuid2230; 11469 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Topfer, Morton L., 2001; cuid2231; 11470 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Torn, Laurence, undated; cuid2232; 11471 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Towl, Ted, 1911; cuid2233; 11472 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Townsend, Paul B., undated; cuid2234; 11473 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Trabold, Andrew Frank, undated; cuid2235; 11474 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Tran, Duong, undated; cuid2236; 11475 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Trani, John M., 1993; cuid2237; 11476 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Trump, John George, 1954; cuid2238; 11477 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Truxal, John, 1957; cuid2239; 11478 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Tsang, Andy, circa 2005; cuid2240; 11479 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Tsao, Robert H. C., circa 1997; cuid2241; 11480 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Tsifrinovich, Vladimir, undated; cuid2242; 11481 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Tsotras, Vassilis J., undated; cuid2243; 11482 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Tucker, Marion, undated; cuid2244; 11483 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Tully, John, undated; cuid2245; 11484 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Turaun, George A., circa 1954; cuid2246; 11485 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Turi, Edith, 1996, circa 2000; cuid2247; 11486 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Turiel, David, undated; cuid2248; 11487 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Tzes, Anthony P., undated; cuid2249; 11488 (Box 8, Folder 131)
- U, 11489
  - Ughetta, Henry L., undated; cuid2250; 11490 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Ugwa, Okay, undated; cuid2251; 11491 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Ujazdowski, T. J., undated; cuid2252; 11492 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Ullman, Robert, undated; cuid2253; 11493 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Ulman, Abraham, 1999; cuid2254; 11494 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Ulman, Hanna A., undated; cuid2255; 11495 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Umanskiy, Vladimir, undated; cuid2256; 11496 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Ungar, J. Stephen, 1956; cuid2257; 11497 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Uzun, Necdet, undated; cuid2258; 11498 (Box 8, Folder 140)
- V, 11499
  - Vacca, Louis N., undated; cuid2259; 11500 (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Vafakos, William P., 1978; cuid2260; 11501 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Valle, Fabio Della, undated; cuid2261; 11502 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Van Cook, Charles F., undated; cuid2262; 11503 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Van Horn, John R., undated; cuid2263; 11504 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Van Norden, E. M., 1955; cuid2264; 11505 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Van Slyke, Richard, undated; cuid2265; 11506 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Van Wagenen, Lindsey, undated; cuid2266; 11507 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Van Wie, Jonathan, undated; cuid2267; 11508 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Van Wynen, Kenneth, undated; cuid2268; 11509 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Varmis, undated; cuid2269; 11510 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Vathke, Otto W., undated; cuid2270; 11511 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Veeraraghavan, Malathi, 2001; cuid2271; 11512 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Veit, Robert C., circa 1966; cuid2272; 11513 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Velazquez, Nydia, 2000; cuid2273; 11514 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Vembenil, Juby, circa 1996; cuid2274; 11515 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Vemuri, Murali K., undated; cuid2275; 11516 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Venner, Julius, undated; cuid2276; 11517 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Vermilye, Rodney J., undated; cuid2277; 11518 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Vesce, V.C., undated; cuid2278; 11519 (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Viets, Herman, circa 1995; cuid2279; 11520 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Vignola, Paul, undated; cuid2280; 11521 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Villa, S. Santos, undated; cuid2281; 11522 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Vincent, Patrick J., undated; cuid2282; 11523 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Vineyard, George, circa 1978; cuid2283; 11524 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Viola, Frank J., undated; cuid2284; 11525 (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Voci, Frank, undated; cuid2285; 11526 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - Vogel, Alice, 1966; cuid2286; 11527 (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - Vogl, Otto, circa 1982, 1994; cuid2287; 11528 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Voltz, Peter, 2000; cuid2288; 11529 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Von Karmen, Theodore, undated; cuid2289; 11530 (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - VonPuttkamer, Jesco H., undated; cuid2290; 11531 (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Vradis, George C., circa 1995; cuid2291; 11532 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Vulanti, Thomas, undated; cuid2292; 11533 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Vybiral, undated; cuid2293; 11534 (Box 8, Folder 175)
- W, 11535
  - Waddell, Russell, circa 1954; cuid2294; 11536 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Wagman, Jack, 1938; cuid2295; 11537 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Wagner, Robert, circa 1975; cuid2296; 11538 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Walker, Burt, undated; cuid2297; 11539 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Walker, W.F., circa 1960; cuid2298; 11540 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Wallace, Richard, circa 1955; cuid2299; 11541 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Wallau, Herman Leon, circa 1954; cuid2300; 11542 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Wallach, Steven J., undated; cuid2301; 11543 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Wallach, Victor, undated; cuid2302; 11544 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Waller, Henry, undated; cuid2303; 11545 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Waller (nee Lepow), Sylvia, circa 1999; cuid2304; 11546 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Walsh, Charles E., undated; cuid2305; 11547 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Walsh, John, undated; cuid2306; 11548 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Walsh, undated; cuid2307; 11549 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Walter, William T., undated; cuid2308; 11550 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Walton, Robert E., undated; cuid2309; 11551 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Wandmacher, F. Cornelius, 1956; cuid2310; 11552 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Wang, Jiun-Nan (Jim), undated; cuid2311; 11553 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Wang, Xiaodong, undated; cuid2312; 11554 (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Wang, Yao, circa 1997; cuid2313; 11555 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Warren, Helen, 1978, 1986; cuid2314; 11556 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Wasilchuk, Steven, undated; cuid2315; 11557 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Wasserman, Steven, undated; cuid2316; 11558 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Waterman, Alan T., circa 1962; cuid2317; 11559 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Watson, Lester W., circa 1959; cuid2318; 11560 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Weaver, Stanley A., circa 1932; cuid2319; 11561 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Weber, Ernst (1901-1966), undated; cuid2320; 11562 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Weber, Sonya, undated; cuid2321; 11563 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Wechsler, Harry C., 1981; cuid2322; 11564 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Wegrzyn, Stanley W., undated; cuid2323; 11565 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Weil, Edward, undated; cuid2324; 11566 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Weil, Robert T., Jr., undated; cuid2325; 11567 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Weill, George, undated; cuid2326; 11568 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Weiman, David N., undated; cuid2327; 11569 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Wein, Joel, undated; cuid2328; 11570 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Weindling, Ralph E., circa 1998; cuid2329; 11571 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Weinman, Eugene A., undated; cuid2330; 11572 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Weiner, James R., undated; cuid2331; 11573 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Weintraub, Ruth, undated; cuid2332; 11574 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Weintraub, Stanley B., undated; cuid2333; 11575 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Weiser, Sidney, 1939; cuid2334; 11576 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Weiss, Gerald, undated; cuid2335; 11577 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Weiss, Marvin D., undated; cuid2336; 11578 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Weissberger, A., undated; cuid2337; 11579 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Weisstuch, Donald N., 1999, 2002; cuid2338; 11580 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Welch, Herbert, 1962; cuid2339; 11581 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Wellbrock, Richard, undated; cuid2340; 11582 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Wendt, undated; cuid2341; 11583 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wendt, Arthur S., undated; cuid2342; 11584 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Wener, Richard, undated; cuid2343; 11585 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Wentzel, Lewis A., circa 1937; cuid2344; 11586 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Wenzel, Alfred C., undated; cuid2345; 11587 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Weseman, Edwin J., circa 1939; cuid2346; 11588 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - West, Warren J., circa 1966; cuid2347; 11589 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Westermann, David, 1976; cuid2348; 11590 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Whalen, Robert J., undated; cuid2349; 11591 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Whang, Sung, 1986; cuid2350; 11592 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Whang (brothers), circa 1955; cuid2351; 11593 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Wheeler, Harold A., circa 1996; cuid2352; 11594 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Whidden, James T., 1956; cuid2353; 11595 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Whipple, Clyde, circa 1955, 1962; cuid2354; 11598 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Whipple, Melville C., undated; cuid2355; 11599 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - White, George R., undated; cuid2356; 11600 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - White, J.L., undated; cuid2357; 11601 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - White, William Augustus, photocopies of 1880 photo; cuid2358; 11602 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Whitehead, Herbert G., undated; cuid2359; 11603 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Whitley, Arthur F., undated; cuid2360; 11604 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Whitmore, Carl, circa 1953; cuid2361; 11605 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Whitmore, Willet F., undated; cuid2362; 11606 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Wich, Emil A., undated; cuid2363; 11607 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Widnall, Sheila, undated; cuid2364; 11608 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Wieber, George A., undated; cuid2365; 11609 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Wiederhorn, Norman, undated; cuid2366; 11610 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Wiedersum, Frederic G., undated; cuid2367; 11611 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wiegand, Dick, 1992; cuid2368; 11612 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Wiener, Anthony J., undated; cuid2369; 11613 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Wigner, Eugene Paul, undated; cuid2370; 11614 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Wikstrand, William C., undated; cuid2371; 11615 (Box 9, Folder 53)